{
    "id": "427d14ddc091478aacc51731d79cffca",
    "title": "Little vs. Few",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was ………………………….. chance of success.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c057e8fa3fe46c3aed36c5d11b0b450"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know ………………………….. man who works in Germany.",
            "description": "Use a before nouns with consonant sounds. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea7be56ab89f4b1b8db77b1c48a8be33"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………………. of my friends to dinner.",
            "description": "All of these are possible here with different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "some",
                "most",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "26b46032bb36469e81771c8d7c4c73bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. of my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Whole",
                "Every"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b913f10d89634e25b4495a49b8b0510a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have written to ……………………….. friend I have.",
            "description": "Use every before a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db003681ef3248c4aafd05cf8c8a352a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hurry up! We haven’t got …………………………. time.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3fa944b1e56947569ebdbfc47a22c97b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Add ………………………….. more salt to the soup.",
            "description": "A little indicates a small quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19885316667443109fbfa5855abce4ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… criminals are non-violent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "Most",
                "Each"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "169a3e5ed96649f2bcf33fec85aeaee8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has so ………………………… followers on social media.",
            "description": "Use many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9dafd8792914e92a654cea66e26fb75"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t …………………………. flowers on the rose.",
            "description": "Use many with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a84f99782b5460d82640588672a2634"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. child needs love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All",
                "Whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18e5678e49404ffa98d204efe07d7ffa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… town was under water.",
            "description": "All goes before the article. Whole goes after the article. ",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "most",
                "whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d899d91a2881414dbd089395b648ba04"
        }
    ]
}